sharebee.com 2011-01-03

# Privacy - Sharebee.com, the one and only online file hosting distribution service.

**Privacy Policy.**

**1\. Your Privacy**  
**Sharebee.com** is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to to improve our own services. All other unnecessary data will be deleted. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.

**2\. What information do we collect? How do we use it?**  
When you visit **Sharebee.com** , we only save your geographical location (country) to improve our ads serving and network performance. To prevent abuses of our services, we save more information (ip addresS) when a visitor uploads a file. All other unnecessary data will be deleted.

**3\. What about "cookies"?**  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We only use cookies to store visitors settings when using our services.

**4\. Will **Sharebee.com** disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**  
**Sharebee.com** does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. **Sharebee.com** may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

**In Summary**  
**Sharebee.com** is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make **Sharebee.com** as simple as possible and to enhance your overall experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by **Sharebee.com** , Inc. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Sharebee.com** also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibliity of the linked site and **Sharebee.com** has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. **Sharebee.com** cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.

**Additional Information**   
Any questions relating to our Legal Agreements and Policies may be directed to **Sharebee.com** using the contact form.
